Guide to the Historic Photographs and Drawings Collection Photo.002
New York University Archives
- Series I: Oversized Photographs and Drawings
  - 15th Annual Dinner of Delta Mu Delta of NYU, December 17, 1927; 20x12 black and white photograph Recto: some surface dirt/fingerprints, curling/planar distortion, tattered edges, white writing from negative Verso: surface dirt/fingerprints, writing in red pencil, stamp in blue ink Condition: Good (Box Shared University Archives 133)
  - 16th Annual Dinner of Delta Mu Delta of NYU, December 15, 1928; 20x12 black and white photograph Recto: some surface dirt/fingerprints, curling/planar distortion, tears at edges, white writing from negative, writing in pencil Verso: heavy surface dirt/fingerprints, writing in red pencil Condition: Good (Box Shared University Archives 133)
  - 18th Annual Dinner of Delta Mu Delta of NYU, December 13, 1930; 20.5x12 black and white photograph Recto: some surface dirt/fingerprints, curling/planar distortion Verso: surface dirt/fingerprints, writing in red pencil, Condition: Good (Box Shared University Archives 133)
  - 19th Annual Dinner of Delta Mu Delta of NYU, December 5, 1931; 20x12 black and white photograph Recto: some surface dirt/fingerprints, curling/planar distortion, tattered edges, white writing from negative Verso: heavy surface dirt/fingerprints, writing in red pencil, stamp in purple ink Condition: Good (Box Shared University Archives 133)
  - 20th Annual Dinner of Delta Mu Delta of NYU, December 3, 1932; 18x10.5 mounted black and white photograph Photo and mounting size are the same Recto: small scratches, writing in white from negative Verso: writing in pencil, yellowing, break in the mounting Condition: Good (Box Shared University Archives 133)
  - 44th Annual Dinner of the NYU Law School Alumni, January 14, 1928; 19x12 black and white photograph Broken into two pieces Recto: heavy surface dirt, white writing from negative, yellowing/discoloration Verso: heavy surface dirt Condition: Poor (Box Shared University Archives 133)
  - 46th Annual Dinner- NYU Law School, January 31, 1931; 20x12 black and white photograph Recto: heavy surface dirt, extreme curling/planar distortion, white writing from negative Verso: heavy surface dirt, stamp in red ink Condition: Good (Box Shared University Archives 133)
  - 48th Annual Dinner of the Alumni Association for NYU Law School, January 31, 1933; 20x12 black and white photograph Recto: top right corner bent, surface dirt, white writing from negative Verso: heavy surface dirt, stamp in purple ink, black fingerprints Condition: Good (Box Shared University Archives 133)
  - 49th Annual Dinner of the Alumni Association of NYU Law School, February 9, 1935; 20x12 black and white photographs Recto: break along surface of photo, planar distortion/curling, writing in white from negative, some surface dirt Verso: heavy surface dirt, writings in pencil, stamp in purple ink Condition: Good (Box Shared University Archives 133)
  - 51st Annual Dinner NYU School of Law Alumni Association, March 16, 1937; 20x12 black and white photograph 2 copies of this item exist Recto: curling/planar distortion, white writing from negative Verso: heavy surface dirt, stamps in purple ink, writings in pencol, deposits from adhesive, yellowing/discoloration Condition: both are good (Box Shared University Archives 133)
  - 52nd Annual Dinner for the NYU School of Law Alumni Association, March 9, 1938; 20x12 black and white photograph Recto: curling/planar distortion, white writing from negative, crease along right side Verso: writings in pencil, stamp in purple ink, heavy surface dirt Condition: Good (Box Shared University Archives 133)
  - Annual Dinner of NYU Law School Alumni Association, March 2, 1940; 22.5x14 this item is broken into 4 pieces Recto: yellowing/discoloration, tears along edges, pressure adhesive repairing tears, writing in white from negative Verso: heavy surface dirt, pressure adhesives to repair multiple tears Condition: Poor (Box Shared University Archives 133)
  - 70th Annual NYU Law Alumni Association Dinner, March 19, 1958; 10x8 mounted black and white photograph Photo and mounting are the same size Verso: strips of pressure adhesive Condition: Good (Box Shared University Archives 133)
  - 75th Annual NYU Law Alumni Association Dinner, April 17, 1963; 10.5x8.5 mounted black and white photograph Photo and mounting size are the same Verso: strips of pressure adhesive Condition: Good (Box Shared University Archives 133)
  - Dinner Given by the Board of Directors of the NYU Law School Alumni Association in honor of Dean Sommer, May 27, 1943; 14x11 black and white photograph 3 copies of this item exist Recto: planar distortion/curling, names of those in attendance, some surface dirt Verso: some surface dirt, stamp in black ink Condition: good (Box Shared University Archives 133)
  - Annual Dinner of the Alumni Association of NYU College Dentistry, April 3, 1936; 20x12 black and white photograph 2 copies of this item exist Recto: white writing from negative Verso: writing in pencil, stamp in black ink, heavy surface dirt Condition: Good (Box 30)
  - NYU College of Dentistry Alumni Association Geoge Washington Hotel, November 19, 1937 (Box 30)
  - 25th Anniversary Dinner- Class of 1914 NYU College of Dentistry, April 28, 1939; 20x12 black and white photograph Recto: bend on top right corner, bottom left corner missing, surface dirt/fingerprints, white writing from negative, rippling along edges, planar distortion/curling Verso: heavy surface dirt Condition: Good (Box 30)
  - Medical Prepatory Banquet, April 14, 1913; 17x11.5 mounted black and white photograph Photo and mounting are the same size Recto: bottom right corner is broken and has been reattached using clear pressure adhesive, extreme discoloration/fading, white writing from negative Verso: large water(?) stain, deposits from adhesive, flaking of mounting Condition: Fair (Box 30)
  - NYU College of Medicine- Class of 1922, May 1, 1937; 14x11 black and white photograph Recto: curling/planar distortion, white writing from negative, tears along the edges, heavy surface dirt Verso: heavy surface dirt Condition: Good (Box 30)
  - 25th Anniversary of the Class of 1912- NYU College of Dentistry, May 20, 1937; 14x11 black and white photograph Recto: heavy surface dirt, curling/planar distortion, white writing from negative Verso: heavy surface dirt, black marks Condition: good (Box Shared University Archives 097, Folder 1)
  - 10th Anniversary Class of 1927 NYU College of Dentistry, April 29, 1937; 20x10 black and white photograph Recto: curling/planar distortion, white writing from negative, some surface dirt along the edges Verso: writing in black pen, black marks, heavy surface dirt Condition: Good (Box 30)
  - 25th Anniversary Dinner- Class of 1912 NYU School of Medicine, May 8, 1937; 20x12 black and white photograph Recto: curling/planar distortion, some surface dirt, black fingerprints, white writing from negative Verso: writing in pencil, stamp in blue ink, surface dirt, Condition: Good (Box 30)
  - 25th Anniversary Dinner Class of 1907 NYU Medical College, February 27, 1932; 20x12 black and white photograph Recto: rippling along edges, curling/planar distortion, Verso: marks in red pencil, heavy surface dirt, black marks Condition: Good (Box 30)
  - NYU College of Dentistry Alumni and Faculty Banquet in honor of Dean A. T. Newman, October 25, 1929; 20x12 black and white photograph 2 copies of this item exist Recto: surface dirt, white writing from negative, curling/planar distortion Verso: heavy surface dirt, black marks, some small tears along edges Condition: Good for both (Box 30)
  - 13th Anniversary Class of 1915 NYU College of Medicine, May 5, 1945; 20x10 black and white photograph Recto: curling/planar distortion, curling/planar distortion, bottom left corner is bent and broken, white writing from negative Verso: heavy surface dirt Condition: Good (Box 30)
  - 20th Anniversary Dinner for Class of 1919 NYU College of Medicine, March 29, 1939; 14x11 black and white photograph Recto: some curling/planar distortion, white writing from negative Verso: heavy surface dirt, large black mark Condition: Good (Box 30)
  - 18th Graduate Course in Surgery Dinner NYU, May 19, 1938; 20x10 black and white photograph Recto: curling/planar distortion, white writing from negative, crease at center Verso: surface dirt, yellowing/discoloration Condition: Good (Box 30)
  - 30th Anniversary Reunion Class of 1914 NYU College of Dentistry, May 17, 1944; 20x10 black and white photograph Recto: some surface dirt, white writing from negative Verso: heavy surface dirt, yellowing, fingerprints Condition: Good (Box 30)
  - 20th Anniversary Reunion Dinner- NYU Dental College class of 1914, April 20, 1934; 14x11 black and white photograph Recto: curling/planar distortion, white writing from negative Verso: heavy surface dirt Condition: Good (Box 30)
  - NYU College of Dentistry, April 16, 1937; 20x12 black and white photograph 2 copies of this item exist Recto: some curling/planar distortion, white writing from negative, bottom left corner bent and broken Verso: heavy surface dirt Condition: Good for both (Box 30)
  - Annual Dinner for NYU Arts and Engineering Alumni, February 5, 1937; 20x12 black and white photograph 2 copies of this item exist Recto: surface dirt, white writing from negative Verso: heavy surface dirt, black marks Condition: Good (Box 30)
  - Class of 1933 NYU School of Arts and Engineering, May 14, 1938; 20x12 black and white photograph 6 copies of this item exist Recto: curling/planar distortion, white writing from negative, rippling along edges Verso: some surface dirt Condition: Good for all (Box 30)
  - College of Dentistry Class of 1928- Collage Photograph, 24x17 black and white photograph collage Recto: yellowing/discoloration, printing in black ink, tears along edges Verso: yellowing/extreme discoloration, heavy surface dirt, clear pressure adhesive repairing breaks and tears Condition: Good (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - College of Dentistry Class of 1916- Collage Photograph, 20x20 mounted black and white collage photograph Recto: large pieces are missing or broken, yellowing/discoloration, heavy surface dirt Verso: yellowing, heavy surface dirt Condition: Poor (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Unidentified NYU Student group with men and two women, man in middle is seated at desk with book open, circa 1910; 14x11 black and white photograph Recto: multiple pieces missing, tears along the edges, yellowing Verso: writings in pencil, mark in blue pencil, heavy surface dirt, heavy surface dirt Condition: Poor (Box Shared University Archives 131)
  - Ringling Brother's and Barnum and Bailey Combined Circus, 1937; 20x12 black and white photograph Recto: curling/planar distortion, bends at corners, curling/planar distortion Verso: heavy surface dirt, stamp in purple ink, black fingerprints Condition: Good (Box Shared University Archives 133)
  - Artistic rendering of meeting of the New York Historical Society, held in the Gothic Chapel of the old NYU building with person identification map, circa 1850; 19x13 mounted black and white print Recto: two mounted images and one label, yellowing Verso: Pressure adhesive holding prints in place Condition: Good (Box Shared University Archives 133)
  - James Bryant Conant, President of Harvard; James Rowland Angell, President of Yale, Harold Willis Dodds, President of Princeton at NYU, June 13, 1934; 16.5x15 mounted, autographed black and white photograph Recto: autographs in black pen, yellowing, some flaking at edges of mounting Verso: mounted letter affixed to the verso with pressure adhesive and clear plastic sheet protector, yellowing/discoloration Condition: Good (Box Shared University Archives 133)
  - SEHNAP event with Dean of Education, President Hester, and other unidentified attendees at unknown event (Gifted by Mrs. Anderson for the NYU Dean's Office), circa 1962-1975; 16.5x13.5 mounted black and white photograph Photo size: 14x11 Mounting size: 16.5x13.5 Recto: stains from adhesive, yellowing Verso: brown stains from liquid(?), writing in pencil, yellowing Condition: Good (Box Shared University Archives 133)
  - WCBS-TV Award Presented to NYU, September 27, 1956; 14x11 mounted black and white photograph Photo and mounting are the same size Recto: wrinkling, bends in photograph, small tears, some adhesive deposits Verso: pieces missing from the mounting, yellowing Condition: Good (Box Shared University Archives 133)
  - Map of NY Harlem Quadrangle, US Geological Survey Map from 1873, 1932; 24x19 printed map with blue ink 4 copies of this item exist General: extreme yellowing/discoloration, multiple breaks and tears Condition: Poor (Flat-file-folder 2 Right)
  - Hand drawn Map of NY Harlem Quadrangle with notes regarding land ownership, circa 1873; 36x23 black printing on fiber paper Recto: severe yellowing/discoloration, very crispy, multiple tears and breaks, pieces missing, writing in pencil and pen, multiple wrinkles Verso: severe yellowing/discoloration, multiple tears and breaks Condition: Poor (Flat-file-folder 3 Right)
  - Traced Map of NY Harlem Quadrangle with notes regarding land ownership, circa 1873; 20x16 pencil drawing on tracing paper Recto: wrinkled, planar distortion, some yellowing, writing in pencil, multiple tears and breaks Condition: Fair (Flat-file-folder 3 Right)
  - NYU Commencement, Washington Square Park, circa 1985-1995; 1 items
  - Group in front of 100 Washington Square East, 1986; 1 items
    This photo came as part of Accession #15.033 and is related to MC 252, the Jill Claster Papers.
  - Class of 1922, NYU Arts and Engineering Colleges 50th Reunion, May 5, 1972 (Flat-file 8, Drawer 3)
  - W.T. Grant portrait, undated (Box Shared University Archives 130)
  - Unknown man holding book with microphone overhead (reverse reads: "Property of George L. Shiebler"), undated (Box Shared University Archives 128)
- Series II: Glass Plates, 1883-1930
  - Delta Iota Delta, 1911 (Box 1, Item 1)
  - Psi Upsilon Party, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 2)
  - NYU Lacrosse Team, 1883-1884 (Box 1, Item 3)
  - "1909" in Butler Hall, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 4)
  - Student Union and Y.M.C.A., 1909 (Box 1, Item 5)
  - Electric Laboratory, 1912 (Box 1, Item 6)
  - NYU Track - Hurdling, 1906 (Box 1, Item 7)
  - NYU Track, circa 1906 (Box 1, Item 8)
  - Rowing Squad, 1908 (Box 1, Item 9)
  - Zeta Psi, 1910 (Box 1, Item 10)
  - NYU Class of 1894, Hats Off (Box 1, Item 11)
  - NYU Football Squad, 1891 (Box 1, Item 12)
  - NYU Class of 1897 (Box 1, Item 13)
  - Old Washington Square Building, Snow, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 14)
  - NYU Class of 1894 (Box 1, Item 15)
  - Psi Upsilon Group, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 16)
  - NYU Lacrosse Team, 1895 (Box 1, Item 17)
  - Fly Lake, 1909 (Box 1, Item 18)
  - Pisek, Bill, Phillips, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 19)
  - Dentz and, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 20)
  - Tally Ho, 1894 (Box 1, Item 21)
  - Tally Ho, 1894 (Box 1, Item 22)
  - NYU Baseball, 1897 (Box 1, Item 23)
  - NYU Class of 1894 (Box 1, Item 24)
  - Cornerstone Lang Hall, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 25)
  - Y.M.C.A. and Bell Tower, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 26)
  - Coming From Chapel, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 27)
  - Halloween Ducking, 1906 (Box 1, Item 28)
  - Fly Lake, 1909 (Box 1, Item 29)
  - NYU Class of 1894, Hats On (Box 1, Item 30)
  - Old Washington Square Building, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 31)
  - Crew and Shell, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 32)
  - NYU Football, 1909 (Box 1, Item 33)
  - Violet Board, 1894 (Box 1, Item 34)
  - Old Washington Square Building, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 35)
  - Old Washington Square Building, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 36)
  - Original Building, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 37)
  - Original Building, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 38)
  - Old Washington Square Building (Bierstadt), circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 39)
  - Old Washington Square Building, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 40)
  - Philomathean Room, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 41)
  - NYU Track - Broad Jumping, 1906 (Box 1, Item 42)
  - NYU Track - Hurdling, circa 1906 (Box 1, Item 43)
  - Psi Upsilon Group, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 44)
  - NYU Rowing Squad, 1908; There are multiple cracks in the top left-hand corner of this glass plate negative. (Box 1, Item 45)
  - Freshman Sophomore Scrimmage, Oct. 1915 (Box 1, Item 46)
  - Freshman Sophomore Scrimmage, Oct. 1915 (Box 1, Item 47)
  - Halloween Ducking, 1906 (Box 1, Item 48)
  - Phi Gamma Delta House, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 49)
  - NYU Class of 1892 (Box 1, Item 50)
  - NYU Track - Pole Vault, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 51)
  - Old Washington Square Building Cut, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 52)
  - Original Building Detail, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 53)
  - Chapel, Original Building, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 54)
  - Chapel, Original Building, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 55)
  - Bleachers, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 56)
  - Pedagogy Library, Washington Square, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 57)
  - Freshman Sophomore Scrimmage, Oct. 1915 (Box 1, Item 58)
  - Fly Lake, 1909 (Box 1, Item 59)
  - Group of Students, 1906 (Box 1, Item 60)
  - NYU Baseball Nine, 1894; There are multiple scratches and cracks across this glass plate negative. (Box 1, Item 61)
  - Freshman Sophomore Scrimmage, Oct. 1915 (Box 1, Item 62)
  - Running Race, 1906 (Box 1, Item 63)
  - NYU Football, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 64)
  - Library of New York University, University Heights Campus, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 65)
  - NYU Baseball, 1906 (Box 1, Item 66)
  - Founders' Memorial, 1911 (Box 1, Item 67)
  - Residence on Campus, House on Schwab Estate, circa 1910 (Box 1, Item 68)
  - "N.Y.U." on Fence, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 69)
  - Old Washington Square Building, 1908 (Box 1, Item 70)
  - NYU Baseball, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 71)
  - Gym in First Location, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 72)
  - Site of Fort #8, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 73)
  - The Bun, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 74)
  - House of Chancellor Henry Mitchell MacCracken, 1910 (Box 1, Item 75)
  - Psi Upsilon House, 1910 (Box 1, Item 76)
  - NYU Chancellor Elmer Ellsworth Brown, circa 1911 (Box 1, Item 77)
  - "Daddy" Falls, 1910 (Box 1, Item 78)
  - Mechanical Engineering Testing Lab, 1912 (Box 1, Item 79)
  - Delta Upsilon House, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 80)
  - NYU Track - Pole Vault, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 81)
  - NYU Chancellor Elmer Ellsworth Brown, circa 1911-1933 (Box 1, Item 82)
  - Gym, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 83)
  - Spectators at an NYU Sporting Event, circa 1906 (Box 1, Item 84)
  - Physics Room, circa 1890-1910; There is a crack in the bottom right-hand corner of this glass plate negative. (Box 1, Item 85)
  - Drawing Room, 1912 (Box 1, Item 86)
  - NYU Baseball Nine, circa 1890-1910; There are multiple cracks across the top left-hand corner of this glass plate negative. (Box 1, Item 87)
  - Group of NYU Athletes, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 88)
  - Dormitory Room, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 89)
  - Students in Butler Hall, circa 1895 (Box 1, Item 90)
  - Crew in Shell, 1908 (Box 1, Item 91)
  - Zeta Psi House, Old, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 92)
  - Physics Lecture, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 93)
  - Student Dinner, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 94)
  - Untitled, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 95)
  - Library, 1895 (Box 1, Item 96)
  - Greek Department Room, Washington Square, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 97)
  - Pedagogy Office, Old Building, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 98)
  - Junior Law Room, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 99)
  - Chancellor's Room, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 100)
  - Old Washington Square Building, Pot Belly Stove, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 101)
  - Untitled, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 102)
  - NYU Track - Pole Vault, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 103)
  - NYU Baseball Players, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 104)
  - Group of NYU Athletes, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 105)
  - NYU Track Athletes, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 106)
  - NYU Track - Shot Put, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 107)
  - NYU Track Athletes, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 108)
  - NYU Track Athletes, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 109)
  - Group of NYU Athletes, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 110)
  - NYU Track Athletes, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 111)
  - NYU Track, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 112)
  - NYU Track Athletes, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 113)
  - The Cross, Chester, circa 1890-1910 (Box 1, Item 114)
  - View from Wash. Bdge., 1890 (Box 2, Item 1)
  - University Heights Railroad Platform, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 2)
  - Northwest View from Physics Building, Butler Hall, 1910 (Box 2, Item 3)
  - Westward View from South Roadway of the Hall of Fame for Great Americans, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 4)
  - General View, University Heights Campus, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 5)
  - General View, University Heights Campus, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 6)
  - Untitled, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 7)
  - View Across University Heights Campus, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 8)
  - Chas. Butler Hall, View From Northwest, 1909; There is a crack across the top right-hand corner of this glass plate negative. (Box 2, Item 9)
  - N.Y. Skin and Cancer Hospital, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 10)
  - Gould Memorial Library Entrance, University Heights Campus, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 11)
  - Gould Memorial Library, University Heights Campus, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 12)
  - Gould Memorial Library, University Heights Campus, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 13)
  - Gould Memorial Library, University Heights Campus, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 14)
  - Gould Memorial Library, University Heights Campus, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 15)
  - Gould Memorial Library, University Heights Campus, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 16)
  - Gould Residence Hall, University Heights Campus, circa 1909-1910; The top right-hand corner of this glass plate negative is broken and very sharp. (Box 2, Item 17)
  - Chemistry Lab, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 18)
  - Tablet on Chemistry Building, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 19)
  - Hall of Fame for Great Americans, University Heights Campus, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 20)
  - Hall of Fame for Great Americans, University Heights Campus, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 21)
  - Hall of Fame for Great Americans, University Heights Campus, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 22)
  - View of University Heights Campus from across the Harlem River, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 23)
  - Hall of Fame for Great Americans, University Heights Campus, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 24)
  - Hall of Fame for Great Americans, University Heights Campus, View From Southwest, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 25)
  - Havemeyer Hall, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 26)
  - Hall of Languages, University Heights Campus, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 27)
  - Hall of Languages, University Heights Campus, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 28)
  - Hall of Languages, University Heights Campus, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 29)
  - Hall of Philosophy, University Heights Campus, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 30)
  - Main Estate, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 31)
  - Schwab House, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 32)
  - Schwab House, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 33)
  - Department of Biology, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 34)
  - Untitled, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 35)
  - Students on Campus, University Heights, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 36)
  - Students on Campus, University Heights, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 37)
  - Students on Campus in snow, University Heights, circa 1909-1910; There are multiple cracks across this glass plate negative. (Box 2, Item 38)
  - Students on Campus, University Heights, circa 1909-1910; There is a verticle crack across the right-hand side of this glass plate negative. (Box 2, Item 39)